Okay, we're going to call today's regular meeting of the Man's Special Utility Authority.
I don't have to do this in that as you know, our fire chief.
Robert Ratzmann did the end of the day.
Thanks Robert.
Let's pray.
You're going to thank you for this day and I thank you for your same Jesus Christ.
I thank you for this Council God and effort that they make to make this community thrive.
I ask God that you best them and best your families.
I thank you God for the city staff and the people in this community.
Thank you for yourselves, Jesus Christ.
Amen.
I mean, why will you do the pledge, please?
I pledge allegiance to the flag of the United States of America.
And to the Republic for which it stands, one nation.
I don't know about it.
You know the visible liberty and justice for all.
Thank you, Brian.
I'm a fuller of public and front non-schederal personal parents.
Anyone who wants to address the authority on any of the agenda items?
They're being non-identified as a consent agenda.
Staff is recommending item 167, which are claims and amendments from October 4 for the consent agenda.
There are no questions and a tangle motion.
No, sir, please.
Second please.
Second.
All.
Johnson.
Western.
All right.
Forster.
Shelts.
Item 9 is new business and he business steam or anyone?
Well, you're on the way to have item 8.
The master service agreement.
A little signature.
Item 8.
Master service agreement.
Olson Engineering.
Chris, do you want me to handle this?
Okay.
Just like to explain what we're doing here.
You might remember at the beginning of the fiscal year.
Instead of filling the vacant city engineers position, we entered into an agreement with Olson Engineering.
Tonight, as a matter of fact, one of the elements of what we hired Olson about will be presented to you.
They were to provide a overall street study program by the end of October, which they have done.
It's going to be presented this evening.
At the end of this month, they'll be doing the same thing with our water and sewer systems as well.
So they're working very well.
But after those two deliverables, they basically had a number of hours that they were going to be helping us with.
And in getting into the program and working on things, things have been going very well.
But sometimes it's hard to track those hours.
And it's also hard to know exactly who authorizes them to do work.
And that's not a problem other than just making sure that we're taking care of the hours properly.
So Olson is suggested modifying their agreement where any other items that we have where they're working with us would basically be on a work order type system.
In other words, they're helping us right now on engineering the new steps in front of this building.
making sure they're ADA compliant, working on that.
They've helped us with items on the new floor at the Solid Waste Disposal Plan,
and they'll be helping us with some other items.
So instead of just trying to track the hours and maybe not have a tight,
they've just suggested that every program that they have,
they have a work list and a work plan that has approved.
We've now the number of hours that's going to be needed.
We know the cost of it, and that way we can take care of the funds a little bit.
So it's just to clean up item that we're bringing you right now,
which I think will help us track the cost and track the progress.
That's the lot better.
Dean, just for clarification our current agreement with him is a professional services agreement.
Correct.
So we don't have to be concerned with bidding practices and things like that.
It's a professional service.
And also this will be appearing on this item.
We'll be appearing on the City Council agenda as well because they're doing work not only on
MSU-I, but also on the City Council.
And so when these task orders are presented,
well those come before the council for approval and advance or how will that work?
We will be working with them on coming up with the task orders and those that by our
code require you approval, they'll be coming to you if they require my approval,
they'll just be approved by me.
Some of them might be relevant to every minor and some of them could be very large.
I wouldn't anticipate after this discussion tonight.
We're probably going to be working with them on a number of road projects.
So we need to have to and those will be significant.
Others like, again, the steps that I mentioned here at the Civic Center,
that's a relatively small project and one I could probably approve.
But we'll be following City Code when it comes to that.
Any other questions for Dean on this particular item?
No.
And so is this just the, in effect that we're approving an amendment, Dean?
Yes, that's an amendment.
That's an amendment where we're creating a master service agreement.
Okay.
So do we have a motion to approve the amendment to our current professional services
agreement with Olson Engineering that creates a master service agreement?
How much motion?
I'll second that.
Well, Paul please.
Forster.
All right.
Shult.
Weston.
All right.
Okay.
Now we're on a new business.
Any new business?
City one.
Staff reports are in your packet.
They're available and they're present if there are any questions.
Anything?
No questions.
Item 11 is trustee community announced.
Okay.
Anything else?
12 is adjourned.
I will make a motion to adjourn.
Do I have a second?
Second.
We'll call a please.
Sult.
All right.
Johnson.
Weston?
Aye.
Forston.
All right.